var questions = [{
    // Question one...
    "question": "What is two + two ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    // Question two...
    "question": "What is three + three ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    // Question three...
    "question": "What is 1 + 2 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    // Question four...
    "question": "What is 2 + 5 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    // Question five...
    "question": "What is 3 + 3 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    // Question six...
    "question": "What is 2 - 5 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    // Question seven...
    "question": "What is 4 - 8 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    // Question eight...
    "question": "What is 12 - 6 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    // Question nine...
    "question": "What is 10 - 5 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    // Question ten...
    "question": "What is 1 - 4 ?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "four",
    "option3": "five",
    "option4": "six",
    "answer": "1"
}]
